[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Other than don't get out (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Other", "than", "do", "n't", "get", "out", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "VB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "ORGAN: Can you quite believe you're in the green jacket, on CNN, you know, talking to the world about being Masters champion?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Can", "you", "quite", "believe", "you", "'re", "in", "the", "green", "jacket", ",", "on", "CNN", ",", "you", "know", ",", "talking", "to", "the", "world", "about", "being", "Masters", "champion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Talking to my favorite person.", "answer_tokens": ["Talking", "to", "my", "favorite", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Yes, but can you believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "can", "you", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Do you go and beat each other up the moment these interviews are over?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "go", "and", "beat", "each", "other", "up", "the", "moment", "these", "interviews", "are", "over", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "We're friends forever.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "friends", "forever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "The friendship?", "question_tokens": ["The", "friendship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What are the lessons?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "lessons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Oh, gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "And performing and having hit records and touring and all that kind of thing, and all the press and the demands and the pressure, it is actually mentally and physically pretty exhausting, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "performing", "and", "having", "hit", "records", "and", "touring", "and", "all", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", ",", "and", "all", "the", "press", "and", "the", "demands", "and", "the", "pressure", ",", "it", "is", "actually", "mentally", "and", "physically", "pretty", "exhausting", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "It's whoo.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "whoo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "-- you know?", "question_tokens": ["--", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "``", "VBZ", "''", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Just celebrate what we're so lucky to be doing still?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "celebrate", "what", "we", "'re", "so", "lucky", "to", "be", "doing", "still", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "When \"Bridesmaids\" really popped and became this huge hit --", "answer_tokens": ["When", "``", "Bridesmaids", "''", "really", "popped", "and", "became", "this", "huge", "hit", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "This is like the sort of thing you dream of, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "like", "the", "sort", "of", "thing", "you", "dream", "of", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 159, "question": "I mean, has it -- has it given you a completely new lease of life as a career?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "has", "it", "--", "has", "it", "given", "you", "a", "completely", "new", "lease", "of", "life", "as", "a", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I feel like it has --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "it", "has", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "And just because you were in a hit movie isn't necessarily going to guarantee that success, you know what I'm saying?", "question_tokens": ["And", "just", "because", "you", "were", "in", "a", "hit", "movie", "is", "n't", "necessarily", "going", "to", "guarantee", "that", "success", ",", "you", "know", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I mean, I think the point is the kind of role model element of that film.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "the", "point", "is", "the", "kind", "of", "role", "model", "element", "of", "that", "film", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "For your kids, maybe?", "question_tokens": ["For", "your", "kids", ",", "maybe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "I just think it's that like edgy kind of \"Saturday Night Live,\" like just edgy, anything goes, women should do what they want and just have that edge, I don't know, you know?", "question_tokens": ["I", "just", "think", "it", "'s", "that", "like", "edgy", "kind", "of", "``", "Saturday", "Night", "Live", ",", "''", "like", "just", "edgy", ",", "anything", "goes", ",", "women", "should", "do", "what", "they", "want", "and", "just", "have", "that", "edge", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "IN", "RB", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "What -- the second time around, when you have all this success again now, people will say to me it's a lot sweeter, because when you stop it and it all goes away, and you watch other people enjoying all the highs and the good stuff, you kind of miss it, even though it's been painful a lot of the time and horrible and you fall out and everything, actually, a part of you really misses it.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "--", "the", "second", "time", "around", ",", "when", "you", "have", "all", "this", "success", "again", "now", ",", "people", "will", "say", "to", "me", "it", "'s", "a", "lot", "sweeter", ",", "because", "when", "you", "stop", "it", "and", "it", "all", "goes", "away", ",", "and", "you", "watch", "other", "people", "enjoying", "all", "the", "highs", "and", "the", "good", "stuff", ",", "you", "kind", "of", "miss", "it", ",", "even", "though", "it", "'s", "been", "painful", "a", "lot", "of", "the", "time", "and", "horrible", "and", "you", "fall", "out", "and", "everything", ",", "actually", ",", "a", "part", "of", "you", "really", "misses", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Is it nice to be able to recapture it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "nice", "to", "be", "able", "to", "recapture", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "We're back together.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "back", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "What is happening here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "happening", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Coming off.", "answer_tokens": ["Coming", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 319, "question": "-- for the way she's been battling this?", "question_tokens": ["--", "for", "the", "way", "she", "'s", "been", "battling", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "I was just going to say --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "going", "to", "say", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Because we eat for a reason, you know what I mean?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "we", "eat", "for", "a", "reason", ",", "you", "know", "what", "I", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "And how -- how is your relationship with your father now?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "--", "how", "is", "your", "relationship", "with", "your", "father", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "It's a little strained at the moment.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "little", "strained", "at", "the", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Do you guys -- do you have one?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "guys", "--", "do", "you", "have", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "There's peace.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "peace", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "But is there actually what you would call a relationship?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "there", "actually", "what", "you", "would", "call", "a", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Yes, somewhat of a relationship.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "somewhat", "of", "a", "relationship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "How would you -- how would you describe it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "--", "how", "would", "you", "describe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Hmmm.", "answer_tokens": ["Hmmm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "-- or is he like this sort of disjointed friend that you've got?", "question_tokens": ["--", "or", "is", "he", "like", "this", "sort", "of", "disjointed", "friend", "that", "you", "'ve", "got", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I wouldn't say that he's like a father figure so much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "say", "that", "he", "'s", "like", "a", "father", "figure", "so", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Why did you play that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "play", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, because it's --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "it", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "-- it's kind of perfect timing, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["--", "it", "'s", "kind", "of", "perfect", "timing", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Whoa.", "answer_tokens": ["Whoa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Is he a better grandfather than father?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "better", "grandfather", "than", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I just think that we need to spend more time with him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "think", "that", "we", "need", "to", "spend", "more", "time", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "What is it like being with all those Baldwins?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "like", "being", "with", "all", "those", "Baldwins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "They are hot.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "are", "hot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Are they funny to be around?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "funny", "to", "be", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Hysterical.", "answer_tokens": ["Hysterical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Alec, he is -- is he the leader of the pack, or not really when they get together?", "question_tokens": ["Alec", ",", "he", "is", "--", "is", "he", "the", "leader", "of", "the", "pack", ",", "or", "not", "really", "when", "they", "get", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "Well, you know, he's the oldest, so he thinks he knows what's right and what's the best thing to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "'s", "the", "oldest", ",", "so", "he", "thinks", "he", "knows", "what", "'s", "right", "and", "what", "'s", "the", "best", "thing", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "No downsides?", "question_tokens": ["No", "downsides", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Several.", "answer_tokens": ["Several", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Stephen?", "question_tokens": ["Stephen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Can I touch it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "touch", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yes, go ahead.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "go", "ahead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "How does it feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "It feels nice.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "feels", "nice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "To be Bubba Watson right now?", "question_tokens": ["To", "be", "Bubba", "Watson", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "It's overwhelming.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "overwhelming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bubba Watson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "But it's genuinely why, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "it", "'s", "genuinely", "why", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Yes, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "It's been a quite extraordinary time for you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "a", "quite", "extraordinary", "time", "for", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Yes, it has.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Why did you want that car so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "want", "that", "car", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "The TV show.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "TV", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Can you quite believe you're in the green jacket, on CNN, you know, talking to the world about being Masters champion?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "quite", "believe", "you", "'re", "in", "the", "green", "jacket", ",", "on", "CNN", ",", "you", "know", ",", "talking", "to", "the", "world", "about", "being", "Masters", "champion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Talking to my favorite person.", "answer_tokens": ["Talking", "to", "my", "favorite", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "But can you believe it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "can", "you", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "The difficulty of the shot and how it played out -- was that the moment for you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "difficulty", "of", "the", "shot", "and", "how", "it", "played", "out", "--", "was", "that", "the", "moment", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "No, I think the six-inch putt to win was the big moment.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "think", "the", "six-inch", "putt", "to", "win", "was", "the", "big", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "What is it inside you that made you look down and say, I'm going for this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "inside", "you", "that", "made", "you", "look", "down", "and", "say", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "I trust everything in -- every ounce of my body, I trust it all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "trust", "everything", "in", "--", "every", "ounce", "of", "my", "body", ",", "I", "trust", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 628, "question": "The moment when you had the six-inch putt to win the Masters, what goes through the golfer's mind when you're six inches away?", "question_tokens": ["The", "moment", "when", "you", "had", "the", "six-inch", "putt", "to", "win", "the", "Masters", ",", "what", "goes", "through", "the", "golfer", "'s", "mind", "when", "you", "'re", "six", "inches", "away", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Masters"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "ORGAN: Other than don't conk it out?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Other", "than", "do", "n't", "conk", "it", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", "IN", "VB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Right, exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Or is it all just focused on the shot?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "all", "just", "focused", "on", "the", "shot", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I definitely wasn't thinking about this show.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "definitely", "was", "n't", "thinking", "about", "this", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "You weren't thinking of me when you won the Masters?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "n't", "thinking", "of", "me", "when", "you", "won", "the", "Masters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "How much of his son are you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "his", "son", "are", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "The first thing that springs to mind is he told me I got two options: I can be a follower or a leader.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "thing", "that", "springs", "to", "mind", "is", "he", "told", "me", "I", "got", "two", "options", ":", "I", "can", "be", "a", "follower", "or", "a", "leader", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "How did you become so composed in such a pressurized moment, if the rest of the time you're all over the place?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "become", "so", "composed", "in", "such", "a", "pressurized", "moment", ",", "if", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "time", "you", "'re", "all", "over", "the", "place", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "ATSON: You know, I recognize that.", "answer_tokens": ["ATSON", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "recognize", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "What lessons can you draw from that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "lessons", "can", "you", "draw", "from", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "Well, I think you got to learn from every situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "got", "to", "learn", "from", "every", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "Is he still the best you've seen, Tiger?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "still", "the", "best", "you", "'ve", "seen", ",", "Tiger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 777, "question": "Bubba Watson, what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["Bubba", "Watson", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "\"America's Got Talent.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "America", "'s", "Got", "Talent", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bubba Watson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 784, "question": "What were you doing there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "doing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "What was the thought process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "thought", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "Golf is boring.", "answer_tokens": ["Golf", "is", "boring", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "What are they going to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "they", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "I know who's not going to be a member.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "who", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "be", "a", "member", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Who, me?", "question_tokens": ["Who", ",", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "You.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 878, "question": "Is she the great love of your life?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "the", "great", "love", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "Oh, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "What did she say to you when you became Masters champion?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "when", "you", "became", "Masters", "champion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "She said -- she didn't say much.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "said", "--", "she", "did", "n't", "say", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 898, "question": "When he's old enough to focus?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "'s", "old", "enough", "to", "focus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 899, "answer": "Yes, and --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 940, "question": "Did you make that yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "make", "that", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 941, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 947, "question": "I don't know, how far is that, about five feet?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "how", "far", "is", "that", ",", "about", "five", "feet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 948, "answer": "About nine feet.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "nine", "feet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 950, "question": "Oh, could be out of your range, couldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "could", "be", "out", "of", "your", "range", ",", "could", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 951, "answer": "Yes, it could be.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "could", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120414pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 960, "question": "What are you doing right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "doing", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 961, "answer": "Don't you worry about me, mate.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "worry", "about", "me", ",", "mate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]